{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Home Designers \u0026 Design-Build Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40208/":{"taskOID":40208,"originalTaskOID":40208,"setID":515,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":1196,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New structure","answerDisplayText":"New structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11432,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition (one story)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (one story)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11434,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Addition (two or more stories)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (two or more stories)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11435,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","answerDisplayText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7254,"questionDisplayText":"Building Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of building is involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11436,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House","answerDisplayText":"House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11437,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Commercial office","answerDisplayText":"Commercial office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11438,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","answerDisplayText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11439,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11440,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Retail store","answerDisplayText":"Retail store","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11441,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Condominium, apartment or town house","answerDisplayText":"Condominum, apartment or town house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5509,"questionDisplayText":"Specific Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please select your specific needs. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11442,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11443,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Technical construction documents","answerDisplayText":"Technical construction documents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Project evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Project evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11445,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Assist with contractor selection","answerDisplayText":"Assist with selection of general contractor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11446,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Review construction","answerDisplayText":"Review construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11447,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11448,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Permit assistance","answerDisplayText":"Permit assistance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200404,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$10,000 - $30,000","answerDisplayText":"$10,000 - $30,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200405,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$30,000 +","answerDisplayText":"$30,000 +","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":1196,"questionDisplayText":"Project Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New structure","answerDisplayText":"New structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11432,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition (one story)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (one story)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11434,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Addition (two or more stories)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (two or more stories)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11435,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","answerDisplayText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11431,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New structure","answerDisplayText":"New structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11432,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition (one story)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (one story)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11433,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","answerDisplayText":"Interior remodel of a few rooms","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11434,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Addition (two or more stories)","answerDisplayText":"Addition (two or more stories)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11435,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","answerDisplayText":"Complete remodel (with or without addition)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7254,"questionDisplayText":"Building Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of building is involved?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11436,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House","answerDisplayText":"House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11437,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Commercial office","answerDisplayText":"Commercial office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11438,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","answerDisplayText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11439,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11440,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Retail store","answerDisplayText":"Retail store","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11441,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Condominium, apartment or town house","answerDisplayText":"Condominum, apartment or town house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11436,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"House","answerDisplayText":"House","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11437,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Commercial office","answerDisplayText":"Commercial office","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11438,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","answerDisplayText":"Residential outbuilding (garage, etc)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11439,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Restaurant","answerDisplayText":"Restaurant","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11440,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Retail store","answerDisplayText":"Retail store","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11441,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Condominium, apartment or town house","answerDisplayText":"Condominum, apartment or town house","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5509,"questionDisplayText":"Specific Needs","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Please select your specific needs. (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11442,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11443,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Technical construction documents","answerDisplayText":"Technical construction documents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Project evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Project evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11445,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Assist with contractor selection","answerDisplayText":"Assist with selection of general contractor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11446,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Review construction","answerDisplayText":"Review construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11447,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11448,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Permit assistance","answerDisplayText":"Permit assistance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11442,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Design drawings","answerDisplayText":"Design drawings","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11443,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Technical construction documents","answerDisplayText":"Technical construction documents","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11444,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Project evaluation","answerDisplayText":"Project evaluation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11445,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Assist with contractor selection","answerDisplayText":"Assist with selection of general contractor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11446,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Review construction","answerDisplayText":"Review construction","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11447,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Would like recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Would like recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11448,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Permit assistance","answerDisplayText":"Permit assistance","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501244,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Budget","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","shortQuestionText":"Approximate budget for design services (excluding product costs)","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200404,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$10,000 - $30,000","answerDisplayText":"$10,000 - $30,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200405,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$30,000 +","answerDisplayText":"$30,000 +","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":200401,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Up to $1000","answerDisplayText":"Up to $1000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200402,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$1000 - $5000","answerDisplayText":"$1000 - $5000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200403,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$5000 - $10,000","answerDisplayText":"$5000 - $10,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200404,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$10,000 - $30,000","answerDisplayText":"$10,000 - $30,000","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200405,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$30,000 +","answerDisplayText":"$30,000 +","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":200480,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"I don't know","answerDisplayText":"I don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11153,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Less than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"Less than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11154,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"More than 2 months","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":30001,"questionDisplayText":"Historical Work","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this location a historical structure?","shortQuestionText":"Is a historical structure?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40208/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40208,"taskName":"Designer - Building","taskDescription":"Design a Building (Non-Architect)","xmTaskDescriptor":"Home Designers \u0026 Design-Build Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":53,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Building Designer architect designers decorator","textMessagingName":"Building Design","rolloverLongDesc":"This person lacks the credentials of an interior designer or an architect but is considered an expert in designing a project.","rolloverShortDesc":"Non-credentialed expert in design.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Design a Building (Non-Architect).  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Design-Build Companies \u0026 Home Designers \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Design-to-Build Contractors","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":3,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Building Designer","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Designer - Building","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Building Designer Need","urlName":"Designer-Building","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Home Designers \u0026 Design-Build Firms - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Building,Designer,architect,designers,decorator,finding,modern,custom,consultants","emcCategoryOid":-12019,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":515,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}